7/18/23, 12:42 PM CV - Thofazzol Hossen

Curriculum Vitae

Personal Information

The purpose of a CV is to show employers that you are suitable for the jobs you are applying for and persuade them to invite you to interview with them. It is a written document which should include information about your skills, qualifications and work experience. I am a hard-working and driven individual who isn't afraid to face a challenge. I'm passionate about my work and I know how to get the job done. I would describe myself as an open and honest person who doesn't believe in misleading other people and tries to be fair in everything I do.

Name: Thofazzol Hossen
Date of Birth: January 1, 1999
Email: thofazzolhossen@gmail.com

• **Phone:** 01892233333

Educational Qualifications

Degree	Institution	Year	Result
Bachelor of Science (Computer Science)	DUET	2020-2024	Running
Diploma	Bangladesh Sweden Polytechnic Institute	2016-2020	3.83
SSC	Shilkhali High School	2011-2016	4.83

Work Experience

Company: XYZ CorporationPosition: Software Developer

• **Duration:** 2014-2019

Company: ABC CorporationPosition: Software Developer

• **Duration:** 2019-2020

Programming Language Skill

- C
- C++
- JavaScript

Team Management Skill

- Additional Co-Curricular Activities Secretary at DUET Computer Society
- Executive Member at DUET Robotics Club
- ICT Secretary at Gungchill, DUET
- Volunteer of DUET Tech Fest 2022
- Volunteer of IDPC 2022